http://www.tasty-chicken-recipes.com/tasty-chicken-recipes-privacy-policy.html

Chicken RecipesHomeWeekly Tasty Chicken RecipesFried Chicken RecipesChicken Salad RecipesEasy Chicken RecipesChicken Breast RecipesBaked Chicken RecipesChicken Marsala Recipes
Support
About Mari & CataContact UsResourcesSite MapLegalPrivacy PolicyTerms of use
Our Privacy Policy
Tasty Chicken Recipes
is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. We strive to offer our visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use personally identifiable information (your name,
e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will NEVER sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. Period.
We collect information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time.
All online visitor data collected by Tasty Chicken Recipes is protected against unauthorized access. We will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organizations.
How we gather information from users:
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services we provide. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, Tasty Chicken Recipes also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.
What we do with the information we collect:
Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.
Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.
We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on Tasty Chicken Recipes to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by Tasty Chicken Recipes and other topics we think you might find of interest.
Personally identifiable information collected by Tasty Chicken Recipes may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it
appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.
Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements:
Tasty Chicken Recipes expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a Tasty Chicken Recipes page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through Tasty Chicken Recipes you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Tasty Chicken Recipes is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy
policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.
While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a
particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. Tasty Chicken Recipes does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.
You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Tasty Chicken Recipes and this policy.
Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. Tasty Chicken Recipes encourages parents to go online with their kids.
Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer:
* Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.
* Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.
* Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated.
Check out the FTC's site for more tips on protecting children's privacy online:
http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html
© tasty-chicken-recipes.com. All Rights Reserved.
